

NADYA BARANAVA

Front-end developer

- Minsk, Belarus
- in linkedin.com/in/nadzeya-baranava-265b45267
- github.com/Nadyushka
- t.me/Nadyushka_Baranova
- → 12nadyall@gmail.com

SKILLS

React / Redux / Redux Toolkit

Axios / Rest API / Postman

JavaScript / TypeScript

Unit tests

Material UI

Formik

HTML5 / CSS3 / SCSS

Storybook

Swagger

GIT

EDUCATION

Frontend developer course it-incubator
Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

Frontend developer course
The Rolling Scope school
Jun 2022 - Oct 2022

Innovation management
BNTU
Sep 2016 - Jun 2018
Mater's degree

Customs affair BNTU Sep 2011 - Jun 2016

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am a Front-End developer. I have an experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/TypeScript. Now I am expanding my skills in frontend development with new technologies. I spend my leisure time reading educational books and improving English and German.

Open for your offers.

EXPERIENCES

English cards - Part-time

Mar 2023 - Present

Start-up project

A team English learning SPA development.

REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT, REDUX-THUNK, REACT-ROUTER-DOM,
FORMIK, MUI, REST API, AXIOS, GIT, POSTMAN, SWAGGER

Todolist

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

Educational project

Todolist was developed with the best React practices. The main idea of the app is to help people to organize their daily or weekly or even monthly tasks the most convenient way.

REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT, FORMIK, MUI, REST API, AXIOS

SOCIAL NETWORK

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Self-education project

SOCIAL NETWORK app was developed with class and functional components, routing, login/logout flow, pagination, form validation, redirections.

REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT, FORMIK, MUI, REST API, AXIOS

LANGUAGES

English - B2

German -B1

Russian - Native